GENEVIEVE PERRON MIGNERON

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

INFO@GEN-MIGNERON.COM

MONTREAL, QC

I am a front end developer with about 6 years of experience. In the past 4 years, I've been evolving in a Rails environment, while using modern JavaScript frameworks such as React and Angular on the front-end side. I am familiar with unit testing, as well as continuous integration tools.

SKILLS

Frontend HTML (HAML, slim, erb) CSS (SASS, SCSS, LESS) JavaScript (Angular, React, jQuery) Backend Ruby PHP C#

General

Version control systems (Git, SVN, TFS) Continous integration tools Unit testing

EXPERIENCE

Glossier

Frontend Engineer March 2017 - December 2018

- Building new features for the company's website
- Implementing GDPR compliance
- Ensuring the website's compliance with accessibility standards
- Write and receive constructive code reviews
- Working in an agile environment

Dynamo

Frontend Engineer December 2014 - March 2017

- Maintaining and improving websites previously built by the company
- Building websites from scratch while following W3C standards and ensuring crossbrowser compatibility

Defacto Interactif

Junior Frontend Engineer August 2013 - September 2014

- Maintaining and improving websites previously built by the company
- Building websites from scratch with Umbraco and Sitecore as a CMS
- Building Facebook contests using their API
- Creating custom newsletter templates

EDUCATION

Maisonneuve College

2010-2012

Technique d'integration multimedia

INTERESTS AND HOBBIES

Photography Travelling Woodworking Skiing Weight lifting Cycling Movies Home automation Video games